stabroeknews.com 2013-05-22

# Privacy Policy - Stabroek News

Thank you for visiting [Stabroek News](http://www.stabroeknews.com/). We respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.  This document outlines such information.

##  **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Stabroek News collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.

Stabroek News’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use its website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our website.

Stabroek News also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and Email addresses. Certain visitors to our website choose to interact with it in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information.

For example, to make a comment on an article we ask that visitors provide a username and valid email address. In this case, we collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with the website. We do not disclose personally-identifying information. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Stabroek News discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Stabroek News’s behalf or to provide services available at the Stabroek News website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Stabroek News website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Stabroek News will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Stabroek News discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Stabroek News believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Stabroek News, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Stabroek News website and have supplied your email address, Stabroek News may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with the website and our services. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Stabroek News takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

##  **Cookies  
**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.

We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

##  ** **Advertising****

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with third party vendors such as Google that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, our advertising partners may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, clickstream information and information about your visits to this and other websites.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads on this site which enables it to serve ads based on your visit to this and other sites on the Internet.  Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

##  **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to this Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
